{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "3(x^2 + 9x + 23)/(2x + 5)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7)/(2x + 5) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) + (x + 4)/(x + 7) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5)\n(x + 7)(x + 7)/(2x + 5)(x + 7) + (2x + 5)(x + 4)/(2x + 5)(x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 7)/(2x + 5) + (x + 4)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 2)(x + 9)/2(x + 6)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 1)/2 * (x + 6)/(x + 6) + 2(x + 3)/(x + 6) * 2/2\n(x + 6)(x + 1)/2(x + 6) + 4(x + 3)/2(x + 6)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 1)/2 + 2(x + 3)/(x + 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 4)(2x + 7)/6(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 4)/3 * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2) + (x + 4)/2(x + 2) * 3/3\n2(x + 2)(x + 4)/6(x + 2) + 3(x + 4)/6(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 4)/3 + (x + 4)/2(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x^2 + 10x + 6)/(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n3(x + 1) * (x + 3)/(x + 3) - (2x + 3)/(x + 3) * 1/1\n3(x + 3)(x + 1)/(x + 3) - (2x + 3)/(x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n3(x + 1) - (2x + 3)/(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(11x^2 + 15x + 6)/2(3x + 2)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 2)/(3x + 2) * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) + (3x + 1)/2(x + 1) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)\n2(x + 1)(x + 2)/2(3x + 2)(x + 1) + (3x + 2)(3x + 1)/2(3x + 2)(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 2)/(3x + 2) + (3x + 1)/2(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 22x + 35)/3(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 5)/3 * (x + 4)/(x + 4) + (3x + 5)/(x + 4) * 3/3\n(x + 4)(2x + 5)/3(x + 4) + 3(3x + 5)/3(x + 4)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 5)/3 + (3x + 5)/(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 4)(x - 1)/3(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 2)/3 * (x + 7)/(x + 7) - 2(x + 3)/(x + 7) * 3/3\n(x + 7)(x + 2)/3(x + 7) - 6(x + 3)/3(x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 2)/3 - 2(x + 3)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-x^2 - 7x - 8)/2(3x + 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 3)/(3x + 5) * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2) - (x + 4)/2(x + 2) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5)\n2(x + 2)(x + 3)/2(3x + 5)(x + 2) - (3x + 5)(x + 4)/2(3x + 5)(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 3)/(3x + 5) - (x + 4)/2(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x^2 + 6x - 7)/3(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 5)/3 * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1) - 2(x + 2)/(2x + 1) * 3/3\n(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/3(2x + 1) - 6(x + 2)/3(2x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 5)/3 - 2(x + 2)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 23x + 12)/2(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 2)/2 * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7) - (x + 1)/(2x + 7) * 2/2\n(2x + 7)(3x + 2)/2(2x + 7) - 2(x + 1)/2(2x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 2)/2 - (x + 1)/(2x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 11x + 8)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7) * (x + 1)/(x + 1) + (3x + 1)/(x + 1) * 1/1\n(x + 1)(x + 7)/(x + 1) + (3x + 1)/(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 7) + (3x + 1)/(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 17x + 19)/(x + 5)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7)/(x + 5) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) - (x + 6)/(3x + 7) * (x + 5)/(x + 5)\n(3x + 7)(x + 7)/(x + 5)(3x + 7) - (x + 5)(x + 6)/(x + 5)(3x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 7)/(x + 5) - (x + 6)/(3x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 12x + 19)/(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 7) * (x + 2)/(x + 2) + (x + 5)/(x + 2) * 1/1\n(x + 2)(2x + 7)/(x + 2) + (x + 5)/(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 7) + (x + 5)/(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(x + 2)(x - 1)/2(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 2)/2 * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) - 2(x + 2)/(3x + 1) * 2/2\n(3x + 1)(x + 2)/2(3x + 1) - 4(x + 2)/2(3x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 2)/2 - 2(x + 2)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 37x + 48)/3(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n2(x + 3)/3 * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) + 3(x + 2)/(3x + 5) * 3/3\n2(3x + 5)(x + 3)/3(3x + 5) + 9(x + 2)/3(3x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n2(x + 3)/3 + 3(x + 2)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 - 3x - 12)/(2x + 5)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1) - (x + 3)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5)\n(2x + 1)(2x + 3)/(2x + 5)(2x + 1) - (2x + 5)(x + 3)/(2x + 5)(2x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 3)/(2x + 5) - (x + 3)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(8x^2 + 35x + 30)/2(x + 3)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3)/2(x + 3) * (x + 4)/(x + 4) + 3(x + 1)/(x + 4) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3)\n(x + 4)(2x + 3)/2(x + 3)(x + 4) + 6(x + 3)(x + 1)/2(x + 3)(x + 4)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 3)/2(x + 3) + 3(x + 1)/(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 11x + 21)/(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 2) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) + (2x + 7)/(x + 7) * 1/1\n(x + 7)(x + 2)/(x + 7) + (2x + 7)/(x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 2) + (2x + 7)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 19x + 7)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 5) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) + 2(x + 1)/(3x + 1) * 1/1\n(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 1) + 2(x + 1)/(3x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 5) + 2(x + 1)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 1)(7x + 17)/3(x + 2)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 1)/3(x + 2) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (x + 2)/(2x + 5) * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2)\n(2x + 5)(2x + 1)/3(x + 2)(2x + 5) + 3(x + 2)(x + 2)/3(x + 2)(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 1)/3(x + 2) + (x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9(-x - 3)/(x + 6)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 3)/(x + 6) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) - 2(x + 3)/(2x + 3) * (x + 6)/(x + 6)\n(2x + 3)(x + 3)/(x + 6)(2x + 3) - 2(x + 6)(x + 3)/(x + 6)(2x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 3)/(x + 6) - 2(x + 3)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(x^2 + 6x - 1)/3(x + 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 6)/(x + 4) * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1) - (x + 5)/3(x + 1) * (x + 4)/(x + 4)\n3(x + 1)(x + 6)/3(x + 4)(x + 1) - (x + 4)(x + 5)/3(x + 4)(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 6)/(x + 4) - (x + 5)/3(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x^2 + 23x + 13)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 4) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4) - (x + 3)/(3x + 4) * 1/1\n(3x + 4)(3x + 4)/(3x + 4) - (x + 3)/(3x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 4) - (x + 3)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x^2 + 14x + 13)/3(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 5)/3 * (x + 2)/(x + 2) + (x + 1)/(x + 2) * 3/3\n(x + 2)(3x + 5)/3(x + 2) + 3(x + 1)/3(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 5)/3 + (x + 1)/(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(8x^2 + 25x + 21)/(x + 4)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 1)/(x + 4) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) + 2(x + 2)/(3x + 5) * (x + 4)/(x + 4)\n(3x + 5)(2x + 1)/(x + 4)(3x + 5) + 2(x + 4)(x + 2)/(x + 4)(3x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 1)/(x + 4) + 2(x + 2)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(x + 2)/2", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 5)/2 * 2/2 + 1/2 * 2/2\n2(3x + 5)/4 + 2/4\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 5)/2 + 1/2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(x^2 + 7x + 9)/3(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 3)/3 * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (x + 1)/(2x + 5) * 3/3\n(2x + 5)(x + 3)/3(2x + 5) + 3(x + 1)/3(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 3)/3 + (x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 4x + 10)/2(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 6)/2 * (x + 4)/(x + 4) - (3x + 7)/(x + 4) * 2/2\n(x + 4)(x + 6)/2(x + 4) - 2(3x + 7)/2(x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 6)/2 - (3x + 7)/(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-x^2 - 22x - 45)/2(3x + 7)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 2)/(3x + 7) * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) - (x + 7)/2(x + 1) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7)\n2(x + 1)(x + 2)/2(3x + 7)(x + 1) - (3x + 7)(x + 7)/2(3x + 7)(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 2)/(3x + 7) - (x + 7)/2(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 7)/2", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 1)/2 * 1/1 + 3 * 2/2\n(3x + 1)/2 + 6/2\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 1)/2 + 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-x^2 + 10x + 47)/(x + 1)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7)/(x + 1) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) - 2(x + 1)/(x + 7) * (x + 1)/(x + 1)\n(x + 7)(x + 7)/(x + 1)(x + 7) - 2(x + 1)(x + 1)/(x + 1)(x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 7)/(x + 1) - 2(x + 1)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(15x^2 + 47x + 33)/3(x + 2)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3)/3(x + 2) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) + (3x + 2)/(3x + 7) * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2)\n(3x + 7)(2x + 3)/3(x + 2)(3x + 7) + 3(x + 2)(3x + 2)/3(x + 2)(3x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 3)/3(x + 2) + (3x + 2)/(3x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x^2 + 12x + 15)/6(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3)/3 * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3) - (2x + 1)/2(x + 3) * 3/3\n2(x + 3)(2x + 3)/6(x + 3) - 3(2x + 1)/6(x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 3)/3 - (2x + 1)/2(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 4x - 7)/6(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 4)/3 * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) - (2x + 5)/2(x + 1) * 3/3\n2(x + 1)(x + 4)/6(x + 1) - 3(2x + 5)/6(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 4)/3 - (2x + 5)/2(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 4)(x + 11)/2(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 6)/2 * (x + 7)/(x + 7) + (x + 1)/(x + 7) * 2/2\n(x + 7)(x + 6)/2(x + 7) + 2(x + 1)/2(x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 6)/2 + (x + 1)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-x^2 - x - 3)/(x + 2)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7)/(x + 2) * (x + 1)/(x + 1) - (2x + 5)/(x + 1) * (x + 2)/(x + 2)\n(x + 1)(x + 7)/(x + 2)(x + 1) - (x + 2)(2x + 5)/(x + 2)(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 7)/(x + 2) - (2x + 5)/(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 13x + 7)/2(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3)/2 * (x + 7)/(x + 7) - (2x + 7)/(x + 7) * 2/2\n(x + 7)(2x + 3)/2(x + 7) - 2(2x + 7)/2(x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 3)/2 - (2x + 7)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x - 10)/(x + 4)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 1)/(x + 4) * (x + 6)/(x + 6) - (3x + 4)/(x + 6) * (x + 4)/(x + 4)\n(x + 6)(3x + 1)/(x + 4)(x + 6) - (x + 4)(3x + 4)/(x + 4)(x + 6)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 1)/(x + 4) - (3x + 4)/(x + 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(4x^2 + 23x + 35)/(2x + 7)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 7)/(2x + 7) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (x + 5)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7)\n(2x + 5)(3x + 7)/(2x + 7)(2x + 5) + (2x + 7)(x + 5)/(2x + 7)(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 7)/(2x + 7) + (x + 5)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 8x + 11)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 3) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) - (3x + 4)/(2x + 5) * 1/1\n(2x + 5)(x + 3)/(2x + 5) - (3x + 4)/(2x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 3) - (3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 3)(x + 4)/(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 4) * (x + 2)/(x + 2) + (x + 4)/(x + 2) * 1/1\n(x + 2)(x + 4)/(x + 2) + (x + 4)/(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 4) + (x + 4)/(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 29x + 37)/3(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 7)/3 * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7) - 2(x + 2)/(2x + 7) * 3/3\n(2x + 7)(3x + 7)/3(2x + 7) - 6(x + 2)/3(2x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 7)/3 - 2(x + 2)/(2x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x^2 + 11x + 11)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n3(x + 2) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) + (x + 4)/(2x + 3) * 1/1\n3(2x + 3)(x + 2)/(2x + 3) + (x + 4)/(2x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n3(x + 2) + (x + 4)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 19x + 23)/6(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7)/3 * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) + (x + 3)/2(x + 1) * 3/3\n2(x + 1)(x + 7)/6(x + 1) + 3(x + 3)/6(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 7)/3 + (x + 3)/2(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x^2 + 25x + 15)/2(x + 7)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 4)/(x + 7) * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) + (2x + 1)/2(x + 1) * (x + 7)/(x + 7)\n2(x + 1)(x + 4)/2(x + 7)(x + 1) + (x + 7)(2x + 1)/2(x + 7)(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 4)/(x + 7) + (2x + 1)/2(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 14x + 37)/(x + 1)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n2(x + 3)/(x + 1) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) - (x + 5)/(x + 7) * (x + 1)/(x + 1)\n2(x + 7)(x + 3)/(x + 1)(x + 7) - (x + 1)(x + 5)/(x + 1)(x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n2(x + 3)/(x + 1) - (x + 5)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 14x + 9)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4) - 3(x + 1)/(3x + 4) * 1/1\n(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(3x + 4) - 3(x + 1)/(3x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 3) - 3(x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 6x + 15)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 1)/2 * (x + 3)/(x + 3) + (x + 6)/(x + 3) * 2/2\n(x + 3)(x + 1)/2(x + 3) + 2(x + 6)/2(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 1)/2 + (x + 6)/(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 4x + 5)/3(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 1)/3 * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1) + 2(x + 2)/3(x + 1) * 3/3\n3(x + 1)(x + 1)/9(x + 1) + 6(x + 2)/9(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 1)/3 + 2(x + 2)/3(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 11x + 23)/6(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 1)/3 * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) + (x + 7)/2(x + 1) * 3/3\n2(x + 1)(3x + 1)/6(x + 1) + 3(x + 7)/6(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 1)/3 + (x + 7)/2(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 13x + 8)/3(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 1)/3 * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (2x + 1)/(2x + 5) * 3/3\n(2x + 5)(x + 1)/3(2x + 5) + 3(2x + 1)/3(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 1)/3 + (2x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x^2 + 31x + 47)/3(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 7)/3 * (x + 5)/(x + 5) + (3x + 4)/(x + 5) * 3/3\n(x + 5)(3x + 7)/3(x + 5) + 3(3x + 4)/3(x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 7)/3 + (3x + 4)/(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(10x + 27)/3(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 7)/(2x + 3) * 3/3 + 2/3 * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3)\n3(2x + 7)/3(2x + 3) + 2(2x + 3)/3(2x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 7)/(2x + 3) + 2/3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 16x + 9)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 6) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1) + 3(x + 1)/(2x + 1) * 1/1\n(2x + 1)(x + 6)/(2x + 1) + 3(x + 1)/(2x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 6) + 3(x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 1)(-x + 5)/2(x + 3)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 1)/2(x + 3) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) - 2(x + 1)/(x + 7) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3)\n(x + 7)(3x + 1)/2(x + 3)(x + 7) - 4(x + 3)(x + 1)/2(x + 3)(x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 1)/2(x + 3) - 2(x + 1)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(3x^2 + 15x + 14)/(3x + 7)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 7) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) + 2(x + 1)/(x + 7) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7)\n(x + 7)(3x + 4)/(3x + 7)(x + 7) + 2(3x + 7)(x + 1)/(3x + 7)(x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 7) + 2(x + 1)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 5x - 10)/2(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 1)/2 * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4) - (3x + 7)/(3x + 4) * 2/2\n(3x + 4)(2x + 1)/2(3x + 4) - 2(3x + 7)/2(3x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 1)/2 - (3x + 7)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 11x + 19)/3(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n2(x + 3)/3 * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2) + (x + 7)/3(x + 2) * 3/3\n6(x + 2)(x + 3)/9(x + 2) + 3(x + 7)/9(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n2(x + 3)/3 + (x + 7)/3(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x^2 + 20x + 17)/2(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 7) * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) + (2x + 3)/2(x + 1) * 1/1\n2(x + 1)(2x + 7)/2(x + 1) + (2x + 3)/2(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 7) + (2x + 3)/2(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(7x^2 + 25x + 24)/6(x + 3)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 5)/2(x + 3) * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2) - (x + 1)/3(x + 2) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3)\n3(x + 2)(3x + 5)/6(x + 3)(x + 2) - 2(x + 3)(x + 1)/6(x + 3)(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 5)/2(x + 3) - (x + 1)/3(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 19x + 17)/2(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 1)/2 * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) + (x + 5)/(3x + 7) * 2/2\n(3x + 7)(2x + 1)/2(3x + 7) + 2(x + 5)/2(3x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 1)/2 + (x + 5)/(3x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x^2 + 2x - 11)/2(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 1)/2 * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) - (3x + 7)/(2x + 3) * 2/2\n(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/2(2x + 3) - 2(3x + 7)/2(2x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 1)/2 - (3x + 7)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 12x + 19)/(x + 3)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 4)/(x + 3) * (x + 4)/(x + 4) + (x + 1)/(x + 4) * (x + 3)/(x + 3)\n(x + 4)(x + 4)/(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 3)(x + 1)/(x + 3)(x + 4)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 4)/(x + 3) + (x + 1)/(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 1)(4x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1) - (3x + 2)/(2x + 1) * 1/1\n(2x + 1)(2x + 3)/(2x + 1) - (3x + 2)/(2x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 3) - (3x + 2)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 8x + 9)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 1) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (x + 4)/(2x + 5) * 1/1\n(2x + 5)(x + 1)/(2x + 5) + (x + 4)/(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 1) + (x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 9x + 23)/3(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7)/3 * (x + 5)/(x + 5) - (x + 4)/(x + 5) * 3/3\n(x + 5)(x + 7)/3(x + 5) - 3(x + 4)/3(x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 7)/3 - (x + 4)/(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 3)(3x + 2)/2(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 1)/2 * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4) + (2x + 1)/(3x + 4) * 2/2\n(3x + 4)(x + 1)/2(3x + 4) + 2(2x + 1)/2(3x + 4)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 1)/2 + (2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 3)(x)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 3) * (x + 1)/(x + 1) - (x + 3)/(x + 1) * 1/1\n(x + 1)(x + 3)/(x + 1) - (x + 3)/(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 3) - (x + 3)/(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5x^2 + 32x + 19)/(x + 2)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7)/(x + 2) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) + 2(x + 3)/(3x + 1) * (x + 2)/(x + 2)\n(3x + 1)(x + 7)/(x + 2)(3x + 1) + 2(x + 2)(x + 3)/(x + 2)(3x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 7)/(x + 2) + 2(x + 3)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5x^2 + 34x + 13)/(x + 6)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 1)/(x + 6) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) + (3x + 1)/(x + 7) * (x + 6)/(x + 6)\n(x + 7)(2x + 1)/(x + 6)(x + 7) + (x + 6)(3x + 1)/(x + 6)(x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 1)/(x + 6) + (3x + 1)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 3)(5x + 7)/(3x + 2)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (2x + 3)/(2x + 5) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)\n(2x + 5)(2x + 3)/(3x + 2)(2x + 5) + (3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(3x + 2)(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) + (2x + 3)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-x + 2)/(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n2(x + 3)/(x + 4) * (x + 4)/(x + 4) - (3x + 4)/(x + 4) * (x + 4)/(x + 4)\n2(x + 4)(x + 3)/(x + 4)(x + 4) - (x + 4)(3x + 4)/(x + 4)(x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n2(x + 3)/(x + 4) - (3x + 4)/(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5x^2 + 33x + 56)/(2x + 7)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7)/(2x + 7) * (x + 4)/(x + 4) + 2(x + 2)/(x + 4) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7)\n(x + 4)(x + 7)/(2x + 7)(x + 4) + 2(2x + 7)(x + 2)/(2x + 7)(x + 4)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 7)/(2x + 7) + 2(x + 2)/(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x^2 + 11x + 25)/3(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 2)/3 * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2) + (x + 7)/(3x + 2) * 3/3\n(3x + 2)(x + 2)/3(3x + 2) + 3(x + 7)/3(3x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 2)/3 + (x + 7)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5x^2 + 27x + 26)/(x + 6)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 1)/(x + 6) * (x + 2)/(x + 2) + (3x + 4)/(x + 2) * (x + 6)/(x + 6)\n(x + 2)(2x + 1)/(x + 6)(x + 2) + (x + 6)(3x + 4)/(x + 6)(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 1)/(x + 6) + (3x + 4)/(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 20x + 49)/(x + 6)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 7) * (x + 6)/(x + 6) + (x + 7)/(x + 6) * 1/1\n(x + 6)(2x + 7)/(x + 6) + (x + 7)/(x + 6)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 7) + (x + 7)/(x + 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n2(x + 1) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) - (3x + 2)/(3x + 7) * 1/1\n2(3x + 7)(x + 1)/(3x + 7) - (3x + 2)/(3x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n2(x + 1) - (3x + 2)/(3x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x^2 + 8x - 7)/2(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 5)/2 * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1) - 2(x + 3)/(2x + 1) * 2/2\n(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/2(2x + 1) - 4(x + 3)/2(2x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(2x + 5)/2 - 2(x + 3)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 7x + 21)/(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 5) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) - (3x + 4)/(x + 5) * 1/1\n(x + 5)(x + 5)/(x + 5) - (3x + 4)/(x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 5) - (3x + 4)/(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x^2 + 39x + 53)/3(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 7)/3 * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) + (x + 6)/(3x + 5) * 3/3\n(3x + 5)(3x + 7)/3(3x + 5) + 3(x + 6)/3(3x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 7)/3 + (x + 6)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 10x + 7)/3(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 2)/3 * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) - (3x + 1)/(2x + 5) * 3/3\n(2x + 5)(3x + 2)/3(2x + 5) - 3(3x + 1)/3(2x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 2)/3 - (3x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 29x + 37)/2(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 5)/2 * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) + 2(x + 3)/(3x + 5) * 2/2\n(3x + 5)(2x + 5)/2(3x + 5) + 4(x + 3)/2(3x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 5)/2 + 2(x + 3)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 2)/(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n2 * (x + 2)/(x + 2) - (x + 6)/(x + 2) * 1/1\n2(x + 2)/(x + 2) - (x + 6)/(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n2 - (x + 6)/(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(x + 5)(2x + 7)/(3x + 7)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 5)/(3x + 7) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) + (x + 5)/(x + 7) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7)\n(x + 7)(x + 5)/(3x + 7)(x + 7) + (3x + 7)(x + 5)/(3x + 7)(x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 5)/(3x + 7) + (x + 5)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x^2 + 30x + 32)/3(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 2)/3 * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) + (x + 6)/(3x + 7) * 3/3\n(3x + 7)(3x + 2)/3(3x + 7) + 3(x + 6)/3(3x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 2)/3 + (x + 6)/(3x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x^2 + 25x + 37)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n2(x + 3) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (3x + 7)/(2x + 5) * 1/1\n2(2x + 5)(x + 3)/(2x + 5) + (3x + 7)/(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n2(x + 3) + (3x + 7)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x^2 + 25x + 28)/3(x + 1)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 4)/(x + 1) * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2) + (3x + 4)/3(x + 2) * (x + 1)/(x + 1)\n3(x + 2)(x + 4)/3(x + 1)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(3x + 4)/3(x + 1)(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 4)/(x + 1) + (3x + 4)/3(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x^2 + 3x - 8)/2(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 2)/2 * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) - (2x + 5)/(3x + 1) * 2/2\n(3x + 1)(x + 2)/2(3x + 1) - 2(2x + 5)/2(3x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 2)/2 - (2x + 5)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(7x^2 + 14x - 6)/(x + 4)(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 7)/(x + 4) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2) - (2x + 5)/(3x + 2) * (x + 4)/(x + 4)\n(3x + 2)(3x + 7)/(x + 4)(3x + 2) - (x + 4)(2x + 5)/(x + 4)(3x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 7)/(x + 4) - (2x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x^2 + 5x - 1)/2(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 5)/2 * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) - (x + 6)/2(x + 1) * 2/2\n2(x + 1)(x + 5)/4(x + 1) - 2(x + 6)/4(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 5)/2 - (x + 6)/2(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(2x + 3)/(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n3(x + 2)/(x + 7) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) + 3(x + 1)/(x + 7) * (x + 7)/(x + 7)\n3(x + 7)(x + 2)/(x + 7)(x + 7) + 3(x + 7)(x + 1)/(x + 7)(x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n3(x + 2)/(x + 7) + 3(x + 1)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x^2 + 16x + 19)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 4)/2 * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3) + (3x + 7)/2(x + 3) * 2/2\n2(x + 3)(3x + 4)/4(x + 3) + 2(3x + 7)/4(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 4)/2 + (3x + 7)/2(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x + 11)/3(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 5)/(x + 1) * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1) + (3x + 7)/3(x + 1) * (x + 1)/(x + 1)\n3(x + 1)(x + 5)/3(x + 1)(x + 1) + (x + 1)(3x + 7)/3(x + 1)(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 5)/(x + 1) + (3x + 7)/3(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 17x + 39)/6(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 4)/3 * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3) + (x + 5)/2(x + 3) * 3/3\n2(x + 3)(x + 4)/6(x + 3) + 3(x + 5)/6(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 4)/3 + (x + 5)/2(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(x^2 + 3x + 4)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 1) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) + (x + 5)/(2x + 3) * 1/1\n(2x + 3)(x + 1)/(2x + 3) + (x + 5)/(2x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(x + 1) + (x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x^2 + 24x + 22)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(x + 7) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4) - (x + 6)/(3x + 4) * 1/1\n(3x + 4)(x + 7)/(3x + 4) - (x + 6)/(3x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(x + 7) - (x + 6)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x + 7)/6", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 5)/3 * 2/2 - 1/2 * 3/3\n2(3x + 5)/6 - 3/6\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n(3x + 5)/3 - 1/2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x^2 + 21x + 35)/2(x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(2x + 3)/2 * (x + 7)/(x + 7) + (2x + 7)/(x + 7) * 2/2\n(x + 7)(2x + 3)/2(x + 7) + 2(2x + 7)/2(x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(2x + 3)/2 + (2x + 7)/(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x^2 + 36x + 23)/3(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n(3x + 4)/3 * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) + (3x + 1)/(3x + 5) * 3/3\n(3x + 5)(3x + 4)/3(3x + 5) + 3(3x + 1)/3(3x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Add:\n(3x + 4)/3 + (3x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x + 1)/(3x + 1)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n2(x + 2)/(3x + 1) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) - 2(x + 1)/(3x + 1) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1)\n2(3x + 1)(x + 2)/(3x + 1)(3x + 1) - 2(3x + 1)(x + 1)/(3x + 1)(3x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "question": "Subtract:\n2(x + 2)/(3x + 1) - 2(x + 1)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"}
]}